(This is a work of fiction. All names, characters, )
(and incidents are products of the author's imagination.)
(All child actors were accompanied by a guardian, )
(and filmed in accordance with labour laws.)
- Heinrich's Law. - Heinrich's Law.
For every major disaster, there are 29 minor incidents on average...
and 300 warning signs.
So, what does that make this situation?
(Revoke the Hangang University Merger)
How did we end up in this mess?
I thought it was just a GitHub push, like a single commit message.
(Dept. of Converged Physical Tech and Global Content Development)
But the errors piled up without any alerts,
and between the conflicts I just glossed over,
what were you and I missing?
What if we were already infected?
- This is a sophisticated virus. - Hey, emergency!
Emergency!
It puts us both at risk,
but strangely, it keeps the system on.
Anyway, what we need to do now is debug.
All the way back to that moment we thought was our safe zone,
let's rewind the timeline.
Find the first log entry of this disaster.
Let's start with your stereotypical image of an engineering student.
Black backpack with a water bottle, a three-fold umbrella on the left,
unstyled hair,
and cheap horn-rimmed glasses.
And on top of that, pants with a questionable fit.
And a plaid shirt you can draw graphs on in a pinch.
But what's missing is a subtitle for the year.
Visit a Korean engineering school now,
and you'll quickly realise...
how distorted your information and narrow-minded your views are.
Ten-dollar horn-rimmed glasses?
These are Gentle Monster, those are Moscot,
and these are Projekt Produkt. Unstyled hair? Give me a break!
They use conditioner, treatments, and even get Brazilian waxes.
Don't get me started on the fantasy of the "Belle of Engineering."
She's pretty, has a great body,
and is a pro at soldering and gaming.
She helps price parts at Yongsan. She's cool with the returnees.
Who is it? Who makes up these stereotypes?
Who is it?
Who the heck is spreading this crap about us?
And another thing.
Since we're not a Seoul university,
campus dramas don't film at our school.
Stuck on the outskirts of the city, where it blizzards on the first day.
It is a little embarrassing.
(Hangang University)
And in the middle of this bizarre weather,
that Tinder Guy asked you to come all the way out to Seoul, right?
Yes.
He asked me to come to his place and fix his desktop?
Said no one was going to be home for a few days.
It's obvious what he was trying to pull.
(First Day of the Semester)
What do you expect from a guy who posts shirtless profile pics?
Says the guy who met his girlfriend on an app?
It's different for guys and girls, okay?
(Kang Dong Won, Junior, Hangang Univ. Fmr. Comp. Eng.)
(Notes: Dept. Rep, aka Kang Dong Won, is taken)
I was explaining a system restore, and then he said he already knew.
Because I'm an engineering student, he wanted to see if I was for real.
(Yang Na Rae, Junior, Hangang Univ. Fmr. Comp. Eng.)
(Notes: BL fangirl, pastor's daughter)
He got defensive and put down my school.
He bragged about his school in Seoul.
How tiresome. So?
I couldn't let it slide, so I dissed my own school right back at him,
and told him the new name of our department.
He told me to stop making it up. He asked, "What department is that?"
- Oppose the Engineering merger! - Oppose!
Save the Department of Computer Engineering!
This is the first build-up to the impending catastrophe.
The merger of Computer Engineering and Modelling, effective this spring.
A combination of buzzwords.
I guess you could call this a bug too.
No less than Dept. Converged Tech and Content Dev.
But really, why should I care?
As long as my sanctuary is intact...
and my world of 1s and 0s is untouchable.
(Joo Yeon San, Junior, Fmr. Comp. Eng.)
(Admitted with top scores)
(Trait: Looks out for number one)
(LOVE.exe)
(Episode 1: What's Your Name?)
If we don't foster interdisciplinary convergence,
we can't navigate the rough seas of the Fourth Industrial Revolution.
A skilled model is not unlike a perfectly coded program.
Don't you think?
Right. They're just broke.
So what are we supposed to call it for short?
Con-Phys? Con-Tech-Glo?
Or wait, Con-Tech-Con?
Guys, let's stop trying to adapt and start fighting back.
A surprise merger during the break? This is basically a scam. Right?
When we enrolled, they kept talking about becoming the "next KAIST."
They promised full scholarships. But look at us and KAIST now.
The only thing we have in common is the Jang Yeong Sil statue.
Even that's different.
KAIST has a full-body statue of him. Ours is, well, as you can see.
So that's what it is. They were prepping this for the merger.
It looks so sloppy and rushed. The art styles are so different.
You're right, Dong Won.
The art styles really are completely different.
Which one is the CompSci major and which one is the Modelling major?
It's so obvious which is which...
that "convergence" hardly seems like the right word.
But having these prickly pretty boys around,
I guess that kind of diversity isn't so bad after all.
What do you mean, "not so bad?" They got a grant for "innovation."
Our scholarships were cut in half, our budget was cut in half,
Our classrooms, labs, and the lounge, all cut in half!
Fellow students, please sign our petition!
Selling our dept. without our say!
To be that young and passionate again.
The blissful ignorance of youth.
- Excuse me, sir. Your name and... - You know, back in my day...
Yet, the school's main contributors haven't uttered a single complaint.
Like your star client and her brother.
It's a win-win situation for everyone.
Right?
Hold on.
That's right. And she's shooting a commercial at Jang Yeong Sil Hall?
Yes.
Always boosting campus revenue, I see.
The director insisted on this place. This lounge really is gorgeous.
So she's shooting that ad with Jennie from Blackpink here?
Not quite. It's Jinny, an older idol but just as famous and popular.
- Jinny? - You know her, right?
Of course, of course.
I'm all about relating to Gen MZ, you know?
In fact, that new department name? That was my idea.
(Dept. of Converged Physical Tech and Global Content Development)
That explains it.
It sounded so trendy.
Now, let's see.
So, about what time will her brother be here?
Well... He wanted to see the new campus.
He should be here any minute now.
The Department of Converged Physical Technology and Global Content Dev...
- What a joke! What a joke! - What a joke! What a joke!
Engineering degree for being tall? Makes no sense! Makes no sense!
Makes no sense! Makes no sense!
Don't just watch, everyone!
Sign the petition to stop the merger!
Please sign the petition. We need your help!
Excuse me...
Could I take a look at that?
(Guarantee Student Rights)
By the way, could you tell me why you're against the merger?
Are you seriously asking because you don't...
You have every right to ask.
You absolutely should ask. This has nothing to do with you...
It's not about you guys personally. Not at all.
Exactly. It's not about individuals. Everyone's special in their own way.
That's a relief.
I'll read this over and come find you again, okay?
Yes, of course.
Got it.
See you around.
Yeah, definitely come back!
Dude, he's gotta be a celebrity. He's way too good-looking.
- We should've gotten his autograph. - He totally is, right?
Darn, he's so tall.
You're a model too, right?
No. I'm a CompSci major.
Why are high school students here? Is there a college info event today?
We heard a celebrity was coming today.
A celebrity?
The model from Match on Wheels! Kang Min Hak!
Will you please keep it down?
She's a huge fan of his, so we all tagged along.
- Pipe down! We'll get kicked out. - Ahem.
Hey, the security guard's here. We'll sign this.
It's okay if we sign this, right?
This is actually just for university members.
Come on. We're part of the local community.
Hey, why are you using my name?
Her name's hilarious, isn't it? Ahn In Dae.
- Gosh, TMI. - That's not TMI.
But you guys really aren't supposed to be signing this.
- Please, not you too. - She's actually kind of funny.
Hilarious.
That's Kang Dong Won for you. Living up to his handsome namesake.
Yeah. "Converged Physical" definitely suits you.
Hey, you two should be the ones joining in.
I don't know if this will help, but...
Converged Technology, or whatever.
If you don't sign, that's what will be printed on your diploma.
But does our department name matter? For developers, experience is key.
You sound like you're in favour of the merger.
Why do you have to put it like that?
- Hey, write neatly in the box. - Okay, okay.
Excuse me, do you know which building C103 is in?
My map app says it's this way, but...
I can show you the way. I happen to be heading there myself.
Really? Thank you.
No, thank you.
Shall we?
See you again!
Take care.
So much for solidarity in our major.
They chose us over the other majors. They knew we were pushovers.
Wow, this lounge is huge.
Sa Ni, you seem kinda excited about this yourself.
Don't tell me you're for the merger, too.
Does the department name matter? Not for a developer.
Not you too!
For a developer, it's all about the gear.
And I just got a new setup.
Intel Core Ultra 200HX and a GeForce RTX 5070.
Data storage is a Super RAID 5.
Okay. Congratulations, I guess.
Excuse me, could you sign this?
Bet you're wondering where I suddenly got all this cash.
Not really.
Here.
I consulted on a TV script for some clueless liberal arts majors.
A TV show?
It was a freelance gig. A client set me up over winter break,
and I met a writer, director, and producer who are big shots.
"We're making a campus drama set in the Computer Engineering Dept."
"A genius coder uninterested in love falls for a cold startup guy."
Sounds boring already, but... what can you do? It's work.
The problem is, the writers are all liberal arts majors...
who know nothing.
Like what the professors are saying in the background...
or what today's engineers or IT professionals in 2025...
how they talk, what they care about. They were completely clueless.
So, with a script full of hundreds, even thousands, of errors,
I started my nitpicky edits,
and they suddenly started complaining.
"We want to focus on the love story..."
"And, you know, a real love story..."
"doesn't unfold before a laptop or behind a lectern."
"Are you an extreme 'T' on the MBTI or something?"
"No. I don't like being defined by MBTI."
So I just took my advance and we terminated the contract.
Which was a total win for me, anyway.
Congratulations again.
Thanks to that, I upgraded to a laptop...
that's about 3.7 times more powerful,
so my compile time will be 2.5 times faster,
and if I use that time to take on 0.8 more freelance gigs a month,
I can get out of this place at least six months sooner.
The reason I'm sharing my stats with you in such detail is...
I know. You're trying to rope me into your project.
I'm being serious.
We're running out of time.
Time?
Seoul's average temp rose last year. Just look outside.
It's March, and we got hit with a sudden cold snap.
I know, right? It even snowed on the first day of the semester.
The college merger is the least of our problems right now.
You know me. If the world were ending,
I'm the type to plant an apple tree.
But we must control what's immediate.
For you, that's the Student Council,
and for me...
Hey, the scholarship results are up!
Hey, they're posted, they're posted!
Sweet!
Are you checking it? Is it posted?
A full ride!
Guys, I got it! Oh my gosh!
Wait, what is this?
Where the heck is this place supposed to be?
What?
This way? Gosh, darn it.
Not interested.
- It's freezing, freezing, freezing. - Excuse me.
Excuse me. Ex-excuse me. Hey, excuse me.
Hey!
What's with this guy?
Sorry, would you happen to know where the Dean's Office is?
Which college's dean? And from what department?
One sec.
Converged Physical Technology...
- Glo... - Dept. of Global Content Dev?
Yes, that's the one.
For the former Comp. Eng. Dean's Office,
head to Jang Yeong Sil Hall.
Jang Yeong Sil... Isn't Jang Yeong Sil Hall this way?
Nope! Most go through the main gate and the College of Human Ecology,
and cross the Cloud Bridge. But if you need the Dean's Office,
it's faster via the Central Library. Got it?
- Right. So I should... - So he didn't get any of that.
In terms of sheer distance, the Human Ecology route is faster,
but that calculation doesn't account for the elevator algorithm.
Elevators were replaced last year,
and now the two are dumb and in sync.
And why do you suppose that is?
Beats me.
Like I said, they must've changed the algorithm.
It used to check each car's distance to the user's selected floor...
and send whichever one was closer.
- So that way... - I'll assume you've got it, then.
So cool. That's the engineering student vibe.
Can I get your Instagram handle?
No, it's just, you look so familiar.
If you're not comfortable, you really don't have to. It's fine.
Give it here.
You have a cute name.
Yang Na Rae.
Na Rae, Na Rae, Yang Na Rae
That's how I'll remember it.
Stop.
No way. 20,000 followers?
So you must be the top dog in the Modelling Major, then.
20,000 followers is nothing.
A classmate has a million followers. See?
A million followers?
For just one of his Reels,
he makes, what, like five grand?
You don't know him? Kang Min Hak.
- For me, that's a lot of money. - It is for everyone.
I understand the scholarship review can be subjective,
and there was some negative wording in my letter of recommendation,
"While not lacking the talent required for academic success..."
"she only seeks her own glory." Is that the part you mean?
This is from Dean Gi Myo Han, I see.
I didn't realise our evaluations would have our names attached,
I may have slipped up last semester, but did you see my GPA is a 4.28?
- Computer Science and Engineering? - Yes.
Major in CompSci and Engineering,
School of Converged Tech and Content.
But you applied as a CompSci Major. That's your old department name.
It's from a duplicate registration, and we can't resubmit it for you,
we've been trying to contact you to correct and resubmit it.
But I never received anything.
Yes, you never picked up. Not our calls or our texts.
We even contacted you yesterday.
That's impossible. If I check my call log...
It is in my call log.
I implemented an SVM model and ran a simple test on my phone,
It's projected to stop 81% of spam. With more data from Jan and Feb...
Okay, okay, guys. Sorry to interrupt your game.
I can't believe my spam beta app made this mistake.
So if I change the name...
to Converged Physical and Global Content...
and apply again, that should fix it right? It's a simple fix?
It was, until yesterday.
It's now a special exception, so you have to start over.
And get the dean's signature.
The dean?
The Peculiar Dean.
We have distinguished guests today, but this spring weather is amazing.
Anyway, this climate crisis these days...
We'd appreciate it if you could be flexible with his classes.
Besides, it's all practical training for his major.
Attendance? That's not a problem.
Just be discreet about it.
- Excuse me. - Yes? Was there something?
I was looking into it,
and CompSci has many classes that could be useful for models.
- Is that so? - Yes, look here.
There's something called Cap Design?
- For making hats or something? - Hats?
- Caps? - Cap...
Oh!
Oh, that. That's, that's called "Capstone Design."
It's a senior class for solving engineering problems, basically.
- Right. I saw one for "running." - Running?
Oh, we models only learn how to walk.
Hey, they teach running in the College of Engineering.
That's probably "Machine Learning." But anyway.
Machine?
Anyway, I'd like to try taking classes like that.
Machine Learning.
Cool Running.
That would be a perfect name for a running crew.
Wow.
Capstone...
Stone?
Thank you again for your time.
Then it's settled. You'll observe my class that day.
- It's great for the school's promo. - Yes, that would be...
- Right. Goodness, thank you. - Yes, of course.
Take care.
- I'm all about that recycling life. - Min Hak! Awesome morning!
Hey.
Right.
Hey!
My follower count suddenly shot up.
I'm at, like, 998,000 now.
Really?
That's great. You were stuck there for a while.
Yeah, and some of my new fans have really funny usernames.
Check this out.
Chun Nyeon Hak, Jong Yi Hak. And get this, Ahn In Dae.
What?
No, if someone's name is Ahn In Dae...
say they come to a fan signing. And I ask, "What's your name?"
and they say, "I'm Ahn In Dae."
I couldn't tell if they aren't a fan,
or if their name is really Ahn In Dae.
It'd be so confusing, right?
This is no time for jokes.
Yeah, like that. I'm pretty good at riffing on stuff.
- Hey, I was wondering... - The lounge is nice. Want to go?
What?
What? I thought you were into that whole engineering student vibe.
We should scout out the engineering building beforehand.
But just a minute ago...
you gave me a look for even bringing up the class.
My bad. I wasn't thinking.
With the merger, that engineering student look could help your career.
That's how we landed that laptop commercial.
That I landed for you.
I know. That's why I suggested wearing my bangs down.
Good call. Forewarned is forearmed.
What does that mean?
(Study Plan)
"By leveraging the IT and tech from the Yeong Sil Scholarship,"
"not for my own personal success,"
"but to help advance humanity?" You? Seriously?
Don't talk to me. The deadline's in ten minutes.
How did you miss that?
They sent so many notices to reapply.
Stop nagging and contribute a line. I'm all out of fancy words.
Guys! You're not going to believe this!
This is huge. Huge!
A student here has one million followers.
- One million followers? - Yep.
That can't be a million students at Hangang University.
So, one of a million followers just happens to be a student here?
Those aren't very surprising odds.
No! Someone with a million followers is in our Modelling Major!
A person with one million followers. Here, on this remote campus.
A celebrity like that has graced us with their presence.
I doubt that empty online popularity matters at Hangang University.
It's not entirely meaningless.
With that kind of following, for every post they upload...
They supposedly get around 5,000.
Wow.
- To even make minimum wage... - What?
They'd have to upload almost 20 posts an hour.
Guess being famous isn't so easy.
What are you talking about? Not 50 cents, 5 thousand dollars.
- What? - That's a whole semester's tuition.
Exactly.
They get to live life that easily?
Who?
- It's Kang Min Hak! - Where?
There he is! Kang Min Hak! Wow, he's so handsome!
He's so freaking hot. So handsome.
Wow, he's seriously good-looking.
Wow, he's unreal!
I have a feeling he's the one. The one with a million followers.
The Modelling Major we were just talking about.
You're handsome, even to other guys.
Loved you on "Match on Wheels!"
- Can I get your autograph? - You're so handsome!
Please sign this for me!
Why does it feel like time is moving in slow motion over there?
That's theoretically possible if the gravity is strong enough.
You can't experience that on Earth. So Na Rae, it's an optical illusion.
Exactly. I mean, time isn't a proven concept.
Oh, come on!
Just look, will you?
When you see beauty, enjoy it. So just enjoy the view!
- But I was here first. - I'm sorry.
I knew it. They're all taking photos.
These nobodies with nothing to share...
are happily doing our marketing for us.
- Min Hak! - Whoa, hey!
We're here to see you!
- Hey, you can't rush him like that! - Hey, you!
- Let go of me! Don't touch me! - What's with all these fangirls?
We're just here to see him!
Teenagers from the suburbs who rarely get to see a celebrity?
An influencer on his level is as popular as a pop idol.
Tell me about it.
What's his deal, anyway?
He gets five grand for a single post.
Why are people so crazy about him?
So cute. Way too cute.
Zoom out, cute. Zoom in, cute.
From this angle or that one? Pure cuteness overload.
Why am I here and not there with them?
I don't think there's anyone as perfect as he is.
He is so handsome, and he is so talented.
I think he's literally the most perfect boy...
I've ever seen.
Professor Eum,
when did you get here?
So you're a K-pop fan too?
Is that guy from BTS?
- Sorry. - No, he is not a K-pop idol.
He is actually from this dating show...
called "Match on Wheels."
On this show,
he won people over with his own special kind of charm.
At first,
no one noticed him among flashier contestants.
Doesn't he look really young?
- He looks like a kid. - I think he's a college student.
- He looks like a college student. - He seems down-to-earth.
He didn't try to stand out,
just quietly cared.
Also fans noticed one of his sexiest traits.
His serious recycling habits.
Cleaning up after everyone isn't easy.
He's just like me, isn't he?
While the other male cast members...
were gossiping behind backs...
and showing their unfiltered macho sides,
he didn't get caught up in it.
No wonder the female cast members...
couldn't help but be drawn to him.
- Back in high school... - Jinny, is Min Hak your type?
I think he's pretty cute.
Midway through the show,
when the girls were all fighting for his attention,
I honestly felt the same.
Maybe it's because the show...
has no script or direction,
just real emotions...
that Min Hak stood out even more.
It's interesting.
That someone like you, an elite, with advanced intellect,
would display such an inexplicable emotional response.
I'm sorry, professor.
What do you mean by that?
Okay, look at this, Nisha.
If there were no crews around,
it'd be kind of hard...
to get a close-up shot like this...
from this angle in this frame.
I'm sorry, what?
Well, unless there was a drone...
the size of a fruit fly...
with a wide lens bigger than itself flying around the cast.
It would make sense. However,
given the physical and mechanical limits of current lens technology,
that's impossible.
And one more thing.
Please forgive me...
for pointing out such an obvious error.
For a rational engineer,
this setup just doesn't fly.
No, this is truly a bare match. No room for tricks or interference.
Right. It's not like the director or writers set this up, right?
He seemed sweet, but he's a beast. He's full of surprises.
- Wait a minute. - What?
- Isn't this game a bit one-sided? - How so?
One look, it's obviously set up for your boy.
The angle opposite that kid is 160 degrees,
and his opponent's angle is, what, about 100 degrees?
Then, according to the law of sines,
for that string to be in equilibrium...
The opponent's force is the kid's times the ratio of sines.
That's 0.9848 over 0.3420, which equals...
- 2.878. - 2.878.
So the other guy has to exert...
2.878 times more force than the boy...
just to maintain equilibrium and not get pulled back.
(Seconds until the game ends)
The "unexpected charm" you mentioned was meticulously engineered.
Gosh, I get it, Joo Yeon San.
I know what you're trying to say,
but actually, I have no clue. How do you calculate all this stuff?
What? It's obvious just by looking at it.
Hey, didn't you say you only had ten minutes left?
Darn it! I need The Peculiar Dean's signature.
Oh, my!
Hey, make sure you have everything. Shouldn't you look more presentable?
Considering The Peculiar Dean's crankiness,
you have a point.
Here, give me your jacket.
You're very high-maintenance, Joo Yeon San.
Go on.
Come on, my friend's a huge fan.
What? Yeah, I'm a fan too.
Not happening. Move along.
Hey...
Hey!
Wait! Hold on!
- Gosh! - What?
What?
- Hey. - What?
Are you okay?
I guess.
Haven't we met somewhere before?
I don't think so.
By conventional standards, I suppose he's handsome.
But what I'm experiencing now is just a personal optical illusion.
The visible light that the human eye can perceive...
is a tiny part of the EM spectrum. Because of this limited range,
we are incapable of fully perceiving the external reality of our subject.
To a more advanced life-form, their appearance might be hideous.
No, it must be hideous.
And your name is?
What? He must think I'm a fan.
No.
I'm Ahn In Dae.
Ahn In Dae?
So you're her!
I can't believe I'm actually meeting you here today.
Ahn In Dae.
- Do they know each other? - No idea.
What the heck is with this guy?
Ahn In Dae...
(Three minutes later)
Someone's in high spirits all of a sudden.
To be honest, I was a little suspicious of you.
What?
I thought maybe you'd bought all those new followers again.
What? You said it felt like a scam. I wouldn't do that again.
Right? You're not the type to do that twice.
But Ahn In Dae, Chun Nyeon Hak...
I figured fans with weird names like that were fake.
But I just met one of them in person.
Man. My bad. I'm sorry.
- Gosh. - Seriously.
Don't worry about it. You're getting surprisingly sharp.
But, kid, once we get a million, ad rates go into a new bracket.
How could I not buy accounts?
We don't need pricey Korean accounts when there are foreign ones.
Anyway, forget about it. Just know I always have your back.
I know.
If you have any issues with me, just let it all out.
Dude, I've got nothing like that.
It's just... I was bothered you went to the dean without me.
I was helping you get your diploma without having to commute out here.
Then you suddenly say you'll take engineering, putting me in a bind.
I can see that.
Sorry. I'll do better.
All right.
I get it. It's about your first love at KAIST.
That's why you have this thing for the "engineering student vibe."
What are you talking about? She wasn't my first love.
We just crossed paths that one time. For 5, maybe 10 minutes?
Was your first love someone else? That quiz kid from grade school?
What are you talking about? Come on! What first love?
Excuse me, is the dean in? I have a scheduled meeting.
You're three minutes late. He waited and then left.
- But I'm only three minutes late. - That's right.
My scholarship is on the line. Could you please just call him?
The dean really hates getting work calls.
You should have come earlier.
- Come back tomorrow. - Today's the application deadline.
That's too bad.
These celebrity autographs...
If you hadn't stopped to get this, you might have been on time.
So I guess he actually came to school.
What a pain.
(To: Ahn In Dae Thanks for everything. Kang Min Hak)
Don't tell me...
this is actually happening!
Back to Heinrich's Law.
For every major disaster,
there are always small warning signs.
How a series of small, absurd moments...
can lead to one monumentally absurd one.
The start of that error code...
Was it the moment our campus became an unwilling runway?
Wow, he's so handsome. Is he a new actor?
No, a part-timer.
I just asked him to be a stand-in. We're good. Thanks!
Okay. Thank you.
Or maybe, at some point in the past that seemed safe,
the disaster had already begun.
New vehicle entered. Redirecting.
Excuse me. Hold on. Sir, you can't park here.
What? There's a spot right here. Why are you telling me I can't park?
As you can see,
it's a handicapped spot. I'm sorry.
- Come on, on a day like today... - I've got to record this jerk.
- You need to be a little flexible. - Gosh, it died.
- It's a handicapped parking spot... - So... Half air, half sound.
What the? What was that noise?
Hey! Were you filming me?
What if I'm still filming? Whose manager are you, anyway?
Hey, Seung Gon, what's going on?
Hey. It's nothing. We're all good.
Look, don't cause a scene. Just move the car, all right?
Excuse me.
- Thanks for your help. - You don't work here, do you?
- Why are you even here? - I work the outdoor section,
but I was coming back from the restroom. So, yes, my bad.
Don't apologise. The real problem is rude people thinking it's a one-off.
Next time, just give them the same attitude.
A battery error.
Wait, so earlier...
- Are you in college? - I'm starting this year. Still 19.
Oh? Me too.
I mean, me too.
Eager to be friends, are you?
No, it's not like that.
All right, then. What's your major?
I'm a modelling major.
Cool. I'm in CompSci.
- I'm off. - Okay.
What?
KAIST? Wow, that's a top-tier school.
Wow, you must be a genius.
This? It was a gift from a senior in high school.
Hold on. Just one second.
What?
Yes, I'm coming. I'm on my way now. Okay.
I don't go to KAIST, though.
I'm starting at Hangang University.
Not that you needed to know that.
Come on, Joo Yeon San. For now, just focus on moving ahead.
Then again, should I look back?
No, "moving forward" is the right idea.
Not the cliche "look forward" way just because he's in front of me.
Back when I didn't know who he was and his smile gave me butterflies,
that might've been the moment the real trouble started.